number four what is the iup pack name
for the following compound so now we
have a cyclohexene derivative so we have
a double bond inside the cyclohexane
ring which makes it cyclohexene and now
it's not arbitrary the way we number we
need for the two carbons participating
in the double bond to be carbons one and
two but there are two options possible
we could either have this be number one
and this be number two or we could have
this be number one and this be number
two and we need to choose the option
that will give any substituents on the
molecule occurring soonest what we end
up realizing is that we have to go 1 2 3
4 5 6 like that there's a few common
errors here some will try to label the
carbon with the chlorine as number one
that doesn't work again it's cyclohexene
which means the carbons participating in
the double bond needs to be carbons one
and two some